Guide to the Stanley Hanna papers SC1256
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanley Hanna papers
1938-2002
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Hanna, Stanley S.
SC1256
24 Linear Feet (16 cartons)
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Biographical / Historical
Stanley Hanna earned an A.B. from Denison University in 1941, and a Ph.D. in Physics from Johns Hopkins University in 1947. He taught at Johns Hopkins until 1955, when he left to work at Argonne National Laboratory. Hanna remained at Argonne National Laboratory until becoming a Professor of Physics at Stanford University in 1963. Hanna died December 27, 2012.
Scope and Contents
Collection consists of research files, drafts, reprints, correspondence, as well as some computer media & audiovisual materials.
Physics.; Nuclear physics.; Hanna, Stanley S.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2015-112
  - Research and files
    - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - S.S. Hanna IAEA, Vienna, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Electric Quadrupole Strength in Ne… Wang, Haeberli, Wissink, Hanna, 1987 Jun (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - purchases (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Analyzers (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 3 Body Disintegrations (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 3 Body, 1951-1957 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Bll Absorption (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Be9 (Ƥ,ƳƳ) curr paper (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Conferences (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Stanford proposals, 1962-1966 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - jobs available, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence Stanford, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - correspondence (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Singh, Segel, Hanna Grace Isobaric Spin in Nuclear Physics, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Sprenkel-Segel, Hanna Mossbauer effect Methodology, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Sprouse, Hanna Nuclear Physics, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - States in between 16.4 and 19.6 MeV R.E. Segel, S.S. Hanna, R.G. Allas, 1965 Aug (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Hanna, Preston The Physical Review, 1965 Aug (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Singh, Segel, Meyer-Schutzmeister, Hanna, Allas Nuclear Physics, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Allas, Hanna, Segel, Singh Meyer- Schutzmeister, Vager Physical Review letters, 1964 Nov (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Allas, Hanna, Meyer-Schutzmeister, Segel, Singh Du Centre National De La Recherche Science, 1964 Jul (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Allas, Hanna, Singh, Sigel, Meyer-Schutzmeister Du Centre National de la Recherche Scien., 1964 Jul (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Sprenkel-Segel, Hanna Journal of the Geochemical Society Geochimica et Cosmochimica Acta, 1964 Jun (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Allas, Hanna, Meyer-Schutzmeister, Segel Nuclear Physics, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Segel, Singh, Allas, Hanna Physical Review Letters, 1963 Apr (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Hanna, Preston, Heberle Proceedings of Intern'l Conference, Pergamon Press, 1963 Aug 5-9 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Preston, Hanna, Heberle The Physical Review, 1962 Dec (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Vienna Hanna, Perlow International Atomic Energy Agency, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Dearnaley, Gemmell, Hanna Nuclear Physics, 1962 Mar (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Hanna, Perlow, Schiffer and Weinman Nature, 1962 Aug (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Meyer-Schutzmeister, Preston and Hanna The Physical Review, 1961 Jun (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Tanner, Hanna Nuclear Physics, 1961 Feb (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Hanna, Meyer-Schutzmeister, Preston, Vincent The Physical Review, 1960 Dec (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Hanna, Segel, Proceedings of the Royal Society, 1960 Jul (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Hanna, Heberie, Perlow, Preston, Vincent Physical Review Letters, 1960 May (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Holland, Lynch, Perlow, and Hanna Physical Review Letters, 1960 Feb (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Hanna, Heberle, Little-john, Perlow, Preston, Vincent Physical Review Letters, 1960 Feb (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Perlow, Hanna, Hamermesh, Littlejohn, Vincent, Preston, Heberle Phy. Rev. Ltrs., 1960 Jan (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Hanna, Heberie, Littlejohn Perlow, Preston, Vincent Physical Review Letters, 1960 Jan (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Fagg, Hanna Reviews of Modern Physics, 1959 Jul (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Holland, Lynch, Hanna The Physical Review, 1958 Nov (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Pruitt, Swartz, Hanna the Physical Review, 1953 Dec (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Frost, Hanna The Physical Review, 1958 May (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Hanna, Meyer-Schutzmeister, Paris Conference, 1958 Paris (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Preston, Hanna The Physical Review, 1958 Jun (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Class, Hanna The Physical Review, 1953 Feb (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Hanna, Meyer-Schutzmeister The Physical Review, 1959 Aug (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Lewis, Charles W. (Dr.), 1967 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Mangelson, Nolan, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Fortune, H. Terry, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Poletti, Alan R. (Dr.), 1966 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Srivastava, Brajesh B., 1966 Aug (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Reddy, K. Rama, 1966 Jun (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Nagatani, K. (Dr.), 1965 Nov-Dec (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Ohlsen, G. G. (Dr.), 1965 Feb (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Ohnuma, Hajime, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Owen, George E. (Prof.), 1964 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Patterson, David O., 1966 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Hausser, Otto (Dr.), 1964 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Hayakawa, Shun-ichiro, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Hickson, Paul J. (Prof.), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Householder, Lynn (Miss), 1967 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Ivanovich, M., 1966 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Jamunathan, Ramanthan, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Kjaer-Pederson, Niels (Dr.), 1966 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Latshaw, Gary, 1966 Jul-Aug (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Leisi, H. J. (Dr.), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Lindley, David (Dr.), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Longworth, Geoffrey, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Marion, Jerry B., 1964 Dec (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Martin, Frederick W. (Dr.), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Phillips, W. R. (Dr.), 1966 Feb (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Raghavan, R. S. (Prof.), 1966 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Rich, W. Foster, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Richard, Patrick (Dr.), 1964 Dec (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Riech, Volkhard (Dr.), 1966 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Seaman, Gregory G. (Dr.), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Thomas, Michael Frank, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Thornton, Stephen T., 1967 (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Thompson, J. C., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Unsold, Hans Jurgen, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - van der Merwe, Philip, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Williams, Norman, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Group notices, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Shadagopan, V. T. + others, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - Khan, Naeem Ahmad, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - Singh, Mohinder (Dr.), 1966 (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - P.N. (Dr.) Rejected, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - B10 (d, ɑɑ)- spect -th calc, cont (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - He3(He3, ρρ)-Th Calc (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - 4 Body Problem (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Li7(ρ,Ƴɑ)-Spect -Th Calc Ƴ Broadening (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Li6(He3, ɑρ)-Th Calc ρ cont (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - B11 (ρ,ɑɑ) spect - Th calc ɑ cont (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - L16 (ɗ, tρ)-spect (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - UO2 - pictures (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Exams- JHU, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - L16 (ɑ, ɑ) (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Li6 (ɑ,Ƴ) B10 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - unlabeled (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - unlabeled (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Advanced Calculus (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Celestial Mechanics (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Colloquia, 1952-1953 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Kinetic Theory notes (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Li7 (d,n) Be8 - spectrum (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Li7 (ρ,Ƴɑ)- spect- data (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Astronomy - Jane (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Math th. Of Economics (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - German, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Electromagnetic Th. Of Light (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Art appreciation (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Historic geology (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Theory of Equations (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - unlabeled (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - unlabeled (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Nuclear Physics Group, 1992 Apr 29 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Binder contents Nuclear physics purchase requisitions, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Warranties (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Travel information (miscellaneous) (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Telephone information, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - express mail, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - (VAX) computer (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Computer network information S.S. Han, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Capital Equipment record (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Expressionist 2.07 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - MacDraft (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Binder contents 2FEV 447, 1991-1995 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Structure of Low-Medium mass nuclei, 1966 Apr 21-23 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Explosives Detector Evaluation, 1988 Mar 21-24 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - The Interaction of High-Energy Photons with Nuclei, 1996 Nov (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - The Interaction of High-Energy Photons with Nuclei, 1996 Nov (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Reaction ΠN →ΠΠN Near Threshold, 1993 May (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Mar dems, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Dems, 1999 Feb (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Dems, 1999 Jan (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Dems, 1998 Dec (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Dems, 1998 Nov (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Dems, 1998 Oct (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Dems, 1998 Sep (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Dems, 1998 Aug (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Dems, 1998 Jul (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Dems, 1998 Jun (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Dems, 1998 May (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Dems, 1998 Apr (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Dems, 1998 Mar (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Dems, 1998 Feb (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Dems, 1998 Jan (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Dems reports, 1997 Oct (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Dems reports, 1997 Dec (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - dems, 1997 Nov (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Kman Reports (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - unlabeled, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - the Energy Dependence of the T Gamow- Teller Strength in p-shell Nuclei Observed in the (n,p) Reaction (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - 19F (p, 8) zone (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Program of the Symposium on Recent Progress in Nuclear Physics with Tandems, 1966 Jul 18-21 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Binder Contents Backup Outputs (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - International Conference on Photonuclear Reactions and Applications, 1973 Mar 26-30 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - 2 FEV 447 PHY 89-13101, 1989 Aug (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Devare, H. G., 1967 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Adams, A., 1967 Aug (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Ashery, D., 1967 Sep (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Berkowitz, Edward H., 1967 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Bray, Kevin H., 1967 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Chaudhri, M. Anwar (Dr.), 1967 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Cottrell, R., 1967 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Davids, Cary N., 1967 Jan (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Fessenden, Peter (Dr.), 1966 Jun (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Gibson, E. F. (Dr.), 1965 Oct (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Hinrichsen, P. F. (Dr.), 1967 Jnauary-Feb (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Huang, Kun-Kuang (Dr.), 1967 Jan (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Jenkin, J. G. (Dr.), 1966 Feb (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Jones, A. D. W., 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Pfeiffer, Loren, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Pronko, John (Dr.), 1966 Mar - May (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Saraceno, Marcos, 1967 Jan (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Segal, Emanuel, 1966 May - Oct (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Shapiro, Mark Howard, 1965 Oct (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Scholz, Wilifred (Dr.), 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Schechter, Hanan (Dr.), 1967 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Slagowitz, Martin B. (Mr.), 1966-1967 Jan-Feb (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Warshaw, Stephen I., 1966 May (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Wielding, Tor (Prof.), 1966 Jun (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Williams, J. M. (Dr.), 1966 Jun-Nov (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Williams, Lawrence E., 1965-1967 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Yaramis, Bahriye, 1967 Mar (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Zaidi, Syed Amir Ali (Dr.), 1965 Oct (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Young, John C. (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Zaidins, Clyde, 1966 Dec (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Zurmuhle, Robert (Dr.), 1966 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Adam, A. (Dr.), 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Allen, J. P., 1966 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Atneosen, Richard (Dr.), 1965 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Barnett, Ross, 1964 Oct - Dec (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Bunch, Stanley M. (Dr.), 1965 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Carrier, David, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Catz, A. L., 1966 Jul - Aug (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Chi, Benjamin E. (Dr.), 1965 Jan (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Chow, Ying-Wei (Dr.), 1966 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Clegg, Thomas B., 1965 Feb - Mar (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Cohen, Bernard L. (Prof.), 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Dallimore, P. J., 1966 Jan- Feb (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Drysale, N. (Dr.), 1965 Jan (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Isospin Chapter (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - International Conference on The Applications of the Mossbauer Effect, 1974 Sep 2-6 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Lawrence Livermore Laboratory Atlas of Photoneutron Cross Sections Obtained with Monoenergetic Photons, 1976 Dec 30 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Gordon Conference on Photonuclear Reactions, 1965 Aug 9-13 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Gordon Conference on Photonuclear Reactions, 1963 Aug 5-9 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Clustering Phenomena in Nuclei: II, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Proceedings of the Summer Study Group on the Physics of the Emperor Tandem Van de Graaff Region, 1965 Jun 21- Jul 16 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Proceedings of the Summer Study Group on the Physics of the Emperor Tandem Van de Graaff Region Volume II, 1965 Jun 21- Jul 16 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Symposium on Nuclear Structure, 1975 Sep 1-6 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Gordon Research Conference on Photonuclear Reactions, 1969 Aug 4-8 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Proceedings of the Summer Study Group on the Physics of the Emperor Tandem Van de Graaff Region Volume III, 1965 Jun 21- Jul 16 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Jahresbericht, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Gordon Research Conference on Photonuclear Reactions, 1971 Aug 16-20 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - unlabeled (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - High Lying O+ and 3- levels in 12C Hanna, Feldman and Suffert, Kurath Phys. Rev, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Coincidence Experiments in Inelastic electron scattering from highly excited states -- Hanna, Nuclear Phys A358, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - S.S. Hanna "Summary Talk" 5th Intn'l Conference on Polarization Phenomenon, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - "Study of the Giant Resonances with Capture Reactions" S.S. Hanna, Mainz, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - SS Hanna (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Study of the Giant Resonances with Capture Reactions S.S. Hanna, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Nuclear Isovector Giant Resonances Excited by Pion Single Charge Exchange (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Mellon Institute Computer Engineering Center (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Progress Report Nuclear Structure Investigations with an FN Tandem Accelerator, 1969 Aug 29 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Progress Report Intermediate Energy and Nuclear Physics Laboratory, 1986-1988 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Second T = 2 of zone (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Returned stuff, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - unlabeled, 1986-1990 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - unlabeled (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - unlabeled (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - unlabeled (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Lifetime Measurements of the first Excited States of B10 and Al28, 1955 Dec (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Polarization of the O16 Gamma Rays L.W. Fagg and S.S. Hanna, 1953 Apr (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Annual Report, 1951 Dec (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Preprints Sent (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Li8 (β) Be8 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Li8 (β) Be8 (ɑ) ɑ - Old Ruins (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Li8 Alphas - spectrograph (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Li7 (ρ,Ƴɑ) Alpha spectrum (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Be9 + D II Spect. Dwgs (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Be9 + D. II Spect Data (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Li8 (β)Be9(ɑ) He4 - find runs (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Etc (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Triple corr calc- B10 (partial) (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Be9 (d,n) B10(Ƴ,Ƴ) B10 - 1.02 - 2.72 com thick target (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Be9 + P theoretical (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - POL Paper (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - N14 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - General UO2 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Astronomy lab (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Economics (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Physics (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Light (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Kinetic Th. Of gases (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - travel (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - travel (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - first drafts (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Ralph (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Isotopes (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - 2.86 - 0.72 B10 correlation- final (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Coupled Rendulum (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Three particle reactions (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - books (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Be9 (d,ɑ) Li7** (ɑ)t - Spect-th calc secondary ɑ + t (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Be9 (d,t) Be8* (ɑ)ɑ - spect - th calc primary t- secondary ɑ (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Reprints (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Reprints (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Binder contents (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Typewriter (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - paper (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - unlabeled (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - superconducting magnets (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - unlabeled (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Material for slides (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Massbaner paper (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Wallace, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Letters - Suny pond, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - unlabeled (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - unlabeled, 1988-1990 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - newsletter, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - French, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Committee for Concerned Scientists (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Berant, Goldberg, Goldring, Hanna, et al Nuclear Physics, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Kuan, Hasinoff, O'Connell and Hanna Nuclear Physics, 1970 Aug (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Hanna, Chapter 12, "Electromagnetic Decay of Isobar Analog States" in Isopin in Nuclear Physics, ed. By D. H. Wlkinson, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Black, O'Connell, Hanna, Latshaw Physics Letters, 1967 Oct (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Hanna, Kalvius and Sprouse International Conference, Tokyo, 1967 Sep (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Kuan, Heikkinen, Snover Riess, Hanna Physics Letters, 1967 Aug (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Electromagnetic Decay of Isobar Analog States S. S. Hanna, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Hours worked records SU 28, 1990-1992 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Dr. William J. Briscoe, UCLA Asst. Prof., 1982 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - unlabeled, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Conferences, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - "Overview… with Emphasis Oak Ridge S.S.H., 1979 Oct (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Paper, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "Giant Multipole Resonances" S. S. Hanna - Erice Summer School, 1976 Jun (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Axel, Drake, Whetsone and Hanna Physical Review Letters, 1967 Dec (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Fisher, Hanna, Healey and Paul Physical Review, 1968 Dec (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Hanna Montreal International Conference on Properties of Nuclear States, 1969 Aug (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Hanna Isopin Conference, Asilomar, 1969 Mar (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Snover, Heikkinen, Riess, Kuan, Hanna Physical Review Letters, 1969 Feb (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Riess, Paul, Thomas and Hanna Physical Review, 1968 Dec (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Kalvius, Sprouse, and Hanna Hyperfine Structure and Nuclear Radiations, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Hanna (invited paper) ICNS, Sendai, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Hanna, Hass, Shkedi and Horowitz Nucl. Phys., 1972 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Glavish, Hanna, Avida, Boyd Chang, Diener Physical review Letters, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Suffert, Feldman and Hanna Part. nuclei, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Hanna, Glavish, Diener, Calarco, Chang, Avida and Boyd Phys. Letters, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Hasinoff, Fisher, Kurjan, and Hanna Nucl. Phys., 1972 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Encycl. Geochem. Environ. Sciences Mossbauer Effect, S.S. Hanna Artcile, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - T.R. Miller, G. D. Sprouse, P.D. Bond, M. Takeda, W.A. Little, and S.S. Hanna Hyperfine Conference, Rehovot, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - P. D. Bond, G.D. Srouse, T.R. Miller, and S.S. Hanna Hyperfine Conference, Rehovot, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Russell, Sprouse, Latshaw Hanna and Kalvius, 1970 May (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Sprouse and Hanna Nuclear Physics, 1969 Nov (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Hasinoff, Fisher, Kuan and Hanna Physics letters, 1969 Oct (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Sprouse, Hanna and Kalvius Physics Review Letters, 1969 Nov (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Nuclear Group (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - unlabeled (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - loan of equipment, 1989 Aug 23 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Kurjan (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Stanford Insurance etc (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Argonne National Laboratory Physics division summary report Annual Review, 1963 Jun (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - NSF Proposal (supplementary budget - G. Fisher), 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Supplement - G. Fisher: Budget Tucker, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - 9Be(3He, ƳƳ) (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - 11C and 15O (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Mosbauer Manuscripts (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Mossbauer Papers (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - "Evidence for a Giant Quadrupole Resonance in 16O, S.S. Hanna, H.F. Glavish, R. Avida, J.R. Calarco et al, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Pulse HT, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Li7* Lifetime (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Reach by phone? (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Least Square Analysis (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Be9 + DII Spect. Calibration (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Li7 (pƳɑ) ɑ (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Polarization of Ƴ Rays (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Li6 (d,t) Li5 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Be (d, n) B10 (Ƴ, Ƴ) B10 - theoretical correlation (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Argonne electronics (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - orders (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Colloquium, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Colloquium, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Purchase orders (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Department of Nuclear Physics Annual Report, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Stanford sit-in, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Plugins notes (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Hanna, Nagatani, Harris, Olness Physical Review, 1971 Jun (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - RARVS, 1991 Mar (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - B11 + B10 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Read comm. (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - reprints (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Meyerhof - Group, 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - unlabeled, 1953-1968 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - unlabeled (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - unlabeled (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - proposals, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence (memo), 1963-1967 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Documents, 1964-1967 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Notes, calculations (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - CERN Courier, 2001 Oct (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, memos (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Figures, notes (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Proposals, paper (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Notes, figures (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, memos (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Documents (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Proposals, paper (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Electronic Relaxation in Rare Earth Metals and alloys, Tm Hanna, Dixon, Fritz, Mahmud, Triplett Von Evatten, Journal de Physique, 1980 Jan (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Little, Jain, Lazarus, Taylor, Triplett, Hanna Hyperfine Interactions, 1980 Apr (Box 8, Folder 36)